Guide to the Rice University Assistant to the President papers: Carl MacDowell, 1963-2001 (bulk 1990-1998) UA 084
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: On Campus - General, 1963 – 2000
  - President
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment, 1994-97 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment, 1996-97 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment/Hopwood, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment/Keneally, Catherine, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment/Search Committee, 1994-95 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action/Office of Equal Employment/Search (Director), 1990 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - (The) Bell Curve, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Chase Bank (formerly Texas Commerce Bank), 1998-99 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Coherent Minor, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Commencement Committee, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Commencement Speaker 1993 (Carter), 1992-93 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Commencement Speaker 1994 (E. Dole), 1993-94 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Commencement Speaker 1995 (Bradley), 1994-95 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Commencement Speaker 1996 (A. Jones), 1995-96 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Commencement Speaker 1997 (Dershowitz), 1996-97 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Commencement Speaker 1998 (Vonnegut), 1996-98 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Commencement Speakers Search Committee, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Commission on Women, 1982, 1985, 1987-89 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Commission on Women, 1990-91 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Commission on Women, 1993-94 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Commission on Women, 1995-96 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Commission on Women, 1994-98 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Commission on Women/Child Care Facilities (Attachments A, B, C), 1992-93 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Commission on Women/Child Care Facilities (Attachments D, E, F), 1992-93 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Women/Child Care Facilities (Attachments G, H, I), 1992-93 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Women/Child Care Facilities (Attachment J), 1992-93 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Women/Child Care Facilities (Attachments K, L, M), 1992-93 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Cost Cutting, 1994-95 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Crisis Management, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Crisis Management, 1990-95 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Crisis Management/Planned Responses, ca 1995 (Folder 1 from Red Binder) General, Hurricane, Fire Explosion, Bomb Threat, Medical, Fondren Library, Physical Plant, Contents, Inclement Weather, Emergency Checklist, Emergency Key Numbers (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Crisis Management/Planned Reponses, ca 1995 (Folder 2 from Red Binder) Emergency Loan Shedding Plan, Emergency Shut Off Points (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Dean's Council, 1991-92 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Diversity, 1994-99 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - E-Mail Issues, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Economic Summit 1990, 1990-91 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Economic Summit 1990, 1990-93 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Entertainment/Receptions, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Feminist Economics, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Courses/Budgets (Mellon and Pew Grants), 1987-92 (Folder 1) (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Courses/Budgets (Mellow and Pew Grants), 1987-91 (Folder 2) (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Courses/Budget, 1988-89 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Courses/Budget, 1988-90 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - (Legal) General Counsel, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - (Legal) General Counsel, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - (Legal) General Counsel, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - General Counsel, 1994-95 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - General Counsel, 1995-96 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - General Counsel, 1995-96 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - General Counsel, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - General Counsel, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - General Counsel, 1996-98 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - General Counsel/Lobbying Disclosure Act of 1995/1996-97 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - General Counsel/(see staff instructions) (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Growth of Rice University, ca 1985 (Folder 1) (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Growth of Rice University, ca 1985 (Folder 2) (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Growth of Rice University, ca 1985 (Folder 3) (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Institutional Growth, 1994-97 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - (1994-95 Task Force on) Institutional Policy Review (DESTROY IN 2005-see folder) (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - (1994-95 Task Force on) Institutional Policy Review/Conflict of Interest (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - (1994-95 Task Force on) Institutional Policy Review/Pending Policy File (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - (1994-95 Task Force on) Institutional Policy Review/Under Review (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Inventory, 1993-94 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Inventory, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Inventory, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Inventory, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Community, 1996-98 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - MacDowell, Carl/Meeting Agendas, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Minority Affairs, 1994-95 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Minority Affairs, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Minority Affairs, 1997-98 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Minority Affairs, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - (President's Council on) Minority Affairs, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - (President's Council on) Minority Affairs, 1994-95 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - (President's Council on) Minority Affairs, 1994-96 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - (President's Council on) Minority Affairs, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Moving Allowances, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Native Americans 1994, 1996-98 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - No Response, 1992-94 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Operations Council, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Operations Council, 1994-96 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Operations Council, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Operations Council, 1996-97 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Operations Council, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Operations Council, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - President's Office, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - President's Office, 1997-98 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Registrar, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Retreat, July 11, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Retreat, January 13, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Rice University Press, 1986-87, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Rupp, George/Agenda Meetings with Neal Lane, 1992-93 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Rupp/Appointment Calendars, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Rupp/Appointments and Contacts Notebook, n. d. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Rupp/Buildings and Grounds Committee, March 16, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Rupp/Buildings and Grounds Committee, March 31, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Rupp/Buildings and Grounds Committee, May 20, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Rupp/Inauguration, 1985-86 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Rupp/Inaugural Committee, 1985 (Folder 1) (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Rupp/Inaugural Committee, 1985 (Folder 2) (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Rupp/Resignation, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Rupp/Resignation, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Rupp/Resignation, 1992-93 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Department of Health and Human Services, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Self Study, 1975-76, 1983-84, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Self Study, c. 1993-94 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Self Study Report, Part II, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, Jan. - Sept. 1993 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, Oct. - Nov. 1993 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, Dec. 1993 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, Jan. - April 1994 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, May 1994 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, June - Aug. 1994 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, Sept. - Dec. 1994 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Self Study Steering Committee, Jan. - May 1995 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1991-92 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1991-93, 1997-98 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Space Facilities Planning Board, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Space Facilities Planning Board, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Space Facilities Planning Board, 1991-93 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Staff Meetings, 1987-91 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Staff Meetings, August 20, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Staff Meetings, September 23, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Staff Meetings, October 29, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Staff Meetings, December 5, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Staff Meetings, January 21, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Staff Meetings, February 13, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Staff Meetings, March 4, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Staff Meetings, March 30, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Staff Meetings, April 21, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Staff Meetings, September 1, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Staff Meetings, October 8, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Staff Meetings, November 11, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Staff Meetings, December 8, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Texas Commerce Bank, 1994-95, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - United Nations Celebration, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - United Way, 1991-93 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - United Way, 1994-95 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Women's Issues, 1993-94 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Provost
    - Admissions, 1991-92 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Admissions, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Admissions, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Admissions, 1993-95 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Application Fees, 1993-94 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Assistant Provost Candidates, 1996-97 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Associate Provost, 1988-91 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Associate Provost, 1993-96 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Associate Provost, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Associate Provost, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Budget Office Report/Student, Faculty, Admission/Financial Aid, Course, Sponsored Research, Misc. Information, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Class Size, 1993, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Classroom Taskforce, 1996-98 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Curriculum Reform, 1994-96 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Curriculum Report, 1996-97 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Curriculum Report, 1995-98 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Dean's Council, 1994-95 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Dean's Council, 1995-96 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - (Mid-Year Conferral of) Degrees, 1997-98 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Degrees Awarded, 1993-94 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Educational Outreach, 1997-98 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Enrollment Management, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Enrollment Management, 1996-98 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Enrollment Management, 1997-98 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Facility Rental Fees, 1991, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, 1992-95 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Faculty, 1996-99 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Appointments and Promotions, 1977-79, 1981-83, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Appointments and Tenure, 1976-78 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Evaluation Forms, 1993-95 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Governance, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1996-97 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1997-98 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Hiring, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Promotion and Tenure, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Promotion and Tenure, 1996-97 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Promotion and Tenure, 1997-98 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1994-97 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Faculty/Staff with International Interests, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Survey, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Tracking - Loose Material (front pocket), 1990-93 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Tracking - Loose Material (back pocket), 1990-93 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Tracking - Division Summary, Faculty Listing/Department, 1990-93 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Tracking - Department Tracking, Sabbatical/LOA, List Tenure Track, Dean's Recruitment Report, Miscellaneous, Candidate Offers/Work File, 1990-93 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Financial Aid, 1991-92 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Financial Aid, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Financial Aid, 1992-95 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Financial Aid, 1993-95 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Financial Aid, 1994-96 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Financial Aid, 1995-97 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Financial Aid, 1995-98 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Financial Aid Task Force Committee, 1992-94 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Grades, 1995-97 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Grades, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic Engineer National Achievement Awards Conference, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Jones School Council of Overseers, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Lovett/Allen Center Remodeling, 1995-96 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - National Youth Leadership Forum on Medicine, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Provost, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Provost, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Provost, 1992-93 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Provost, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Provost, 1994-96 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Provost, 1995-96 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Provost, 1996-97 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Provost, 1996-98 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Provost, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Provost/Search Committee, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Provost/Search Committee, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Provost/Search Committee, 1993-94 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Provost/Search Committee (Marcia Citron), 1993-94 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Provost/Search Committee (Laurie Feinswog), 1993 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Provost/Search Committee (Anigone Kostas), 1993-94 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Rankings: Universities, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Registrar, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Registrar, 1992-94 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Registrar, 1995-96 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Registrar, 1996-98 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Registrar/Computer Security (Prime), 1994 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Registrar/Computer Security (Prime), 1994 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Rice Commissions, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Rice Fellows, 1993, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Scienta, 1991-94 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Shell Development Space Site, 1992-93 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Space and Facilities Planning Board, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Space and Facilities Planning Board, 1996-97 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1994-97 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1996-98 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1996-98 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Student Aid Foundation Enterprise, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Student Loans, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Student Loan, 1998-2000 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Teaching Evaluations, 1997 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Texaco Star Challenge, 1989-95 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Tuition, 1988, 1991, 1993-94 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Tuition, 1995-97 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Tuition, 1994,1997-99 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Tuition Plan, 1993-94 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Tuition Plan, 1993, 1998-99 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - (Prepaid) Tuition Plan, 1997-99 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - University Librarian, 1991-92 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - University Professor, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Vice Provost for Administration Search, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Registrar/Computer Security – Cassettes, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Vice President for Advancement and University Relations
    - Alumni Affairs, 1992-94 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1994-95 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1994-95 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Events, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - (Distinguished) Alumni and Meritorious Service Awards, 1991-94 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Assistant Vice President for Development Search, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Costello, Kathryn, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Costello, Kathryn, 1994-96 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Costello, Kathryn/Costello, Daniel, 1994-96 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Development, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Development, 1993-94 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Development, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Development/Gifts, 1992-94 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Development/Mitchell, Douglas, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Development Requests/Gillis, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Development/Rupp Trips, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Division of Redeployment, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Donor Relations, 1994-95 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Events and Functions, 1992-95 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Events and Functions, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - External Affairs Computer Conversion, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Fund Council, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Fund Council, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Fundraising Results, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - General Announcements, 1994-95 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - General Announcements, 1995-96 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming, 1995-96 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Kimball, Mark, Executive Director of Development, 1993-94 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Strategy Committee, 1992-93 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Lovett/Brown Day, 1994-95 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - March of Dimes/Plaque, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - March of Dimes/Walkathon, 1994-95 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - March of Dimes/Walkathon, 1994-95 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - March of Dimes/Walkathon, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Minimum Tax/Charitable Giving, 1990-93 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Rice Associates Events, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Rice Associates Events, 1995-96 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Parent's Program at Rice, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Rice Historical Society, 1995-96 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Rice News Office, 1992-93 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Rice News Office, 1993-94 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Rice News Office, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Rice University Press, 1992-93 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Rice University Press, 1994-95 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Sallyport, 1992-93 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Scholarship Receptions, 1994-95 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - South Texas Law School Search, 1994-95 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - University Relations, 1992-93 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - University Relations, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - University Relations, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - University Relations, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs, 1993-94 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs, 1994-95 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Ads, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search- Candidates, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search- Candidates, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Candidates (Costello, Kathryn), 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Candidates Resumes A-C, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Candidates Resumes D-L, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Candidates Resumes M-Q, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Candidates Resumes R-T, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-Fox Morris, 1994-95 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Vice President Development and Alumni Affairs/Search-General Information, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Vice President External Affairs, 1993-94 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Vice President External Affairs, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Vice President External Affairs, 1994-95 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Vice President for External Affairs
    - Alumni Affairs, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Board, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Alumni/Honors Committee, 1990-91 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Alumni/Honors Committee, 1991-92 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Alumni/Honors Committee, 1992-93 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Capital Campaign, 1987-89 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Capital Campaign, 1992-93 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Case Statement (University Standing of the Highest Grade), 1992 (final copy catalogued Call No. LD 4711 .R297 R54 1991 WRC) (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Celebration, 1990-92 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Committee, 1990-91 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Development/Correspondence, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Development/Meeting Agenda Books, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /January 31, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /February 17, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /March 6, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp/April 2, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /April 20, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /June 4, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /June 25, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /August 20, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Development/Meeting with Rupp /October 6, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Development/Trip Files-Chicago, August 26-27, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Development/Trip Files-Los Angeles, December 13-15, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Development/Trip Files-New York, June 15-17, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - DDevelopment/Trip Files-New York, February 9-10, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Development/Trip Files-New York, September 30, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Development/Trip Files-San Francisco, June 27-28, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Development/Trip Files-San Francisco, January 7-9, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Development/Trip Files-San Francisco, April 26-28, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Development/Trip Files-San Francisco, July 9-10, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Development/Trip Files-Washington, D.C., November 16-17, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Events and Functions/President's Executive Luncheon, 1991-92 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Gift Giving/Rice, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - News and Publications, 1991-92 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - News and Publications/ABC Nightline-Rice University, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - News and Publications/Berryhill, Michael, Executive Director, 1991-92 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - "A Race for Life"/Location Agreement, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - President's Report (Rupp), 1992 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - President's Statements (Rupp), 1992-93 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Real to Reel/Convicts, September 17, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Rice News Office, 1993-94 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Rice Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Sallyport, 1990-92 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Summit of the Minds, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - University Relations, 1991-92 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Vice President for External Affairs, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Vice President for External Affairs/Search, 1989-90 (Box 111, Folder 3)